<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <title>Open Buddha</title>
 <link href="http://openbuddha.com/mozilla.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://openbuddha.com/"/>
 <updated>2012-03-06T16:15:32-08:00</updated>
 <id>http://openbuddha.com/</id>
 <author>
   <name>Al Jigong Billings</name>
   <email>albill@openbuddha.com</email>
 </author>



  <entry>
    <title>The Attack of an Open Request</title>
    <link href="http://openbuddha.com/2012/03/07/the-attack-of-an-open-request/" />
    <updated>2012-03-07T21:28:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://openbuddha.com/2012/03/07/the-attack-of-an-open-request</id>
    <content type="html">
      &lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/albill/6773360154/&quot; title=&quot;Untitled by albill, on Flickr&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://farm8.staticflickr.com/7038/6773360154_c7fb437f91.jpg&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; height=&quot;375&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Apparently, asking for people to support an open community and to keep divisive speech seen to attack community members off of Planet Mozilla is seen by at least one of the Planet Mozilla peers as an &quot;attack.&quot; See his comment  &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.mozilla.com/planet/2012/03/06/concerns-with-planet-content/#comment-41285&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can only shake my head at this and wonder how people just don't get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One person calls for enshrining in law the traditional second class position of members of the LGBT community in society on the basis of his personal beliefs. A second calls for an open community. Does the peer call the first person's post an attack? No. But apparently responding to it with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.openbuddha.com/2012/03/06/supporting-an-open-mozilla/&quot;&gt;yesterday's post by me&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;does&lt;/em&gt; constitute an attack. How's that work?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I certainly never to expect to be chastised for my position and have a peer suggest I take yesterday's post down for standing up for people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I said yesterday included the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;One thing that I cannot abide is prejudicial actions within that community which go against its basic ethos of inclusiveness and betterment for the good of all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;I encourage all Mozillians to donate to one of the many public organizations supporting equal rights for the LGBT community. This is the best way to send a message in support of inclusiveness and an open Mozilla community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm not going to apologize for wanting an inclusive Mozilla that treats my queer brothers and sisters (and they are all of our brothers and sisters, as well as wives, husbands, fathers, mothers, even sons and daughters) as welcome members and co-creators in what we're trying to accomplish. We are a community based on openness and the betterment of society. Isn't that what we're here for? Not simply to participate in making cool Internet software?&lt;/p&gt;


      
    </content>
  </entry>
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Supporting an open Mozilla</title>
    <link href="http://openbuddha.com/2012/03/06/supporting-an-open-mozilla/" />
    <updated>2012-03-06T16:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://openbuddha.com/2012/03/06/supporting-an-open-mozilla</id>
    <content type="html">
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.openbuddha.com/images/550x-mozilla-dinosaur-logo.png&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;231&quot; align=&quot;right&quot; hspace=&quot;5&quot; vspace=&quot;5&quot;&gt;I'm a proud Mozillian. I've worked at the Mozilla Corporation since June of 2007. I came there after working at Microsoft for nine years and was tired of working in a closed system that seemed to be designed for the good of a few people only. Working with my coworkers and the larger Mozilla Community composed of everyone interested in Mozilla (not just Firefox) and contributing to it has been a great boon to me over the last few years. It was a breath of fresh air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing that I cannot abide is prejudicial actions within that community which go against its basic ethos of inclusiveness and betterment for the good of all. Today, a fellow community member decided to send a post to &lt;a href=&quot;http://planet.mozilla.org&quot;&gt;Planet Mozilla&lt;/a&gt;, the public face of the community through its blogs, that was prejudicial against the queer community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with quite a few others, I was outraged at this but, as the individual has said, it is his blog and he can say what he wants on it. He has his bully pulpit but, as it turns out, so do I.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided to respond today with this post but, more importantly, I also gave a donation to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.eqca.org&quot;&gt;Equality California&lt;/a&gt; in the name of my fellow community member. Why Equality California? Well, I live here and we're actively fighting a battle on the very issue, gay marriage, that was at the root of the person's post. EC is very heavily engaged in this fight. As EC says on their site:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equality California (EQCA) is the largest statewide lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender rights advocacy organization in California. Over the past 13 years, Equality California has strategically moved California from a state with extremely limited legal protections for LGBT individuals to a state with some of the most comprehensive civil rights protections in the nation. Equality California has partnered with legislators and advocates to successfully sponsor more than 80 pieces of pro-equality legislation. EQCA continues to advance equality through legislative advocacy, electoral work, public education and community empowerment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another option, for UK community members, is &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.stonewall.org.uk/what_you_can_do/donate_to_stonewall/&quot;&gt;Stonewall&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I encourage all Mozillians to donate to one of the many public organizations supporting equal rights for the LGBT community. This is the best way to send a message in support of inclusiveness and an open Mozilla community.&lt;/p&gt;


      
    </content>
  </entry>
 
</feed>